Next, we need to edit the sleeve.
In the virtual model arm position, click on the center point.
In this blue point, create a straight line point.
After selecting the extension tool, click on the center point at the top, then click on the center point at the bottom to create a baseline.
Then rotate a side of the plate to make the bottom have more volume.
After creating, click on the center point at the bottom.
After creating, adjust the shape of the plate.
In the process of stretching the bottom, click on the control key to change it along the original rhythm.
Then select the line at the bottom of the sleeve plate, also click on the control key to stretch along the original rhythm.
Then select the line at the top of the sleeve plate, click on the control key to change it along the original rhythm.
The sleeve has been a little bit twisted here.
It's because we just fixed it to the virtual model with a sewing needle.
So the width of the sleeve is not enough.
After stretching, simulate the clothes.
After simulation, you can see that the sleeves are much smoother.
Then some adjustments, then some adjustments.
Including the length of the sleeve.
And widen the sleeve a little bit.
After the modification, turn the bottom straight line point to the curve line point to make the curve line smoother.
Then use the edge curve point tool to adjust the curve line at the bottom.
After simulation, reduce the particle diameter to 10 to get a better simulation effect.
After creating the sleeve plate,
then create the opening plate to make the embroidery effect.
Use the rectangle tool to drag the 2D window to create an opening plate.
You can use the edge curve tool to select the width of the plate.
Usually 15 to 20 centimeters is more suitable.
Then use the line sewing tool to sew these plates together.
After sewing, arrange the arrangement points near the wrist.
After arranging, use the positioning ball to move it to a position that can cover the virtual model wrist.
After this simulation, you won't be able to pass your arm.
You can widen the sleeve bottom according to your needs.
After that, you have to make a belt.
The waist plate can be shortened a little bit.
It's also the same as before.
Use the edge curve measurement tool to click on the waist.
Since the clothing measurement board has passed the belt and the sleeve,
you need to adjust its diameter.
After adjustment, you can use the edge curve measurement tool to select the measurement board to adjust its position.
After modifying the diameter, you need to move the measurement board to apply the change.
Then we have finished the measurement board removal.
You can remove the extra plates with the same operation as before.
If therated pins may disappear during the process, please add them.
Eliminate excess plates.
Remove the excess plates.
After cutting some of the plate, the felt is not close enough.
Pull out some ropes to tighten the lower board
Next, let's make a belt plate
First select the bottom 100 part of the front and back pieces
In the attribute editor, look at their 2D line length
Then use the rectangle tool to click on the 2D window
Width is the measurement value, height is set according to need
After creation, you can check the 3D window plate effect and adjust it
Adjust the width according to need
After arranging the plate, select the line cutting tool
First click on the belt, then press the Shift key
In the same direction as the belt
Click on the top line each time, then release the Shift key
Then merge the sides together
After merging, change to the leather surface, the surface will be more flat
And then we will see the result
After changing, switch to the leather surface, the surface will be more flat
Next, we will change the width of the belt
First click on the belt
Then click on the belt